<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Papyros</title>
    <description>Papyros is a modern operating system which adheres to Google&#39;s Material Design guidelines and is based on Arch Linux.
</description>
    <link>http://papyros.io/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://papyros.io/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 16:42:23 +0000</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Apr 2015 16:42:23 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Repository for Early Testing</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We now have an initial package repository for users to try out the Papyros shell on ArchLinux!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;&lt;strong&gt;DISCLAIMER&lt;/strong&gt;: Currently, there are packages for x86_64 architecture only, as the qt5 packages are big and will take time to compile again for i686. Keep in mind this is very much in a pre-alpha state, and many things are not implemented yet. The packages themselves should work though, as I’ve tested them locally. No guarantees though!&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;First, add the following lines to your &lt;code&gt;/etc/pacman.conf&lt;/code&gt; file, above the default repositories:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;[papyros]
SigLevel = Never
Server = http://dash.papyros.io/repos/$repo/$arch
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Then, run&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;pacman -Syu
pacman -S papyros-shell
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;You can then test the shell by running it in a new window on top of your desktop:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;pre&gt;&lt;code&gt;papyros-shell
&lt;/code&gt;&lt;/pre&gt;

&lt;p&gt;It’s still very much in early development, though; the network indicator doesn’t work, and you can’t even start apps in the shell yet. Those features will land over coming weeks.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Happy testing!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Michael Spencer, Papyros founder and lead developer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 08 Feb 2015 04:07:20 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://papyros.io/2015/02/08/repository-for-early-testing.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://papyros.io/2015/02/08/repository-for-early-testing.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Monthly Status Update 1/15</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I had originally planned to do weekly status updates, but I’ve been busy focusing on actual development and normal life, so I’ve only had time to do one update so far. So, we’ll turn the updates into monthly updates instead. I’ll start off by calling this the January update so as to get another one in at the end of February.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The biggest news since our first update is that we’ve settled on a new name - Papyros! (The old name, Quantum OS, was trademarked by an existing company). Our website is now &lt;a href=&quot;http://papyros.io&quot;&gt;papyros.io&lt;/a&gt;, and you can follow us on &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/113262712329378697012&quot;&gt;Google+&lt;/a&gt; or join our &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/communities/109966288908859324845&quot;&gt;Google+ community&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;new-team-members&quot;&gt;New Team Members&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;I’d like to welcome several new designers and developers to our team who have shown continued great contributions in code and designs.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our design team consists of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Myself, Michael Spencer (well, I’m a developer, not a professional designer, but I care a lot about design)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Josh Gray&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Christopher Spencer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Andrea Del Sarto&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Christoph Laier&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;And our development team consists of:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Michael Spencer (that’s me again)&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Bogdan Cuza&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Ricardo Vieira&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to this awesome team and to everyone else who has show interest, given support, or contributed to the project.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;overall-os-progress&quot;&gt;Overall OS progress&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work on the overall OS is progressing nicely. Our design team has done some great mockups for the installer and some of the core apps, including the web browser and calculator. We also have our first packages available in the AUR, which you can install as &lt;a href=&quot;https://aur.archlinux.org/packages/papyros-shell/&quot;&gt;papyros-shell&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Work is also starting on a build server to host packages so users don’t have to compile everything from scratch, which takes a very long time, especially in VirtualBox. Unfortunately, there are some issues with the build tooling on the server, but hopefully that can be worked on soon.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;material-design-framework&quot;&gt;Material Design framework&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of work has gone into polishing the Material Design framework. Some of the features that have been implemented include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;An improved dialog component&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A FAB/action button&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Dropdown and navbar overflow menu&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Slider component&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved textfield&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Switch to QtQuick Controls for the PageStack&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improved ink animations&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material/graphs/contributors&quot;&gt;17 developers&lt;/a&gt; who have contributed to the framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;desktop-shell&quot;&gt;Desktop shell&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Lots of work has gone into Papyros shell, and it’s getting closer and closer to at least being semi-usable as a full desktop session. We also reached a significant milestone by being able to run it as a Wayland session from GDM using Qt 5.5’s eglfs bindings.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some of the features that have been implemented in the past two months include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A music control widget in the widgets/notification drawer&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The sound indicator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The power indicator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;A classic layout, similar to Chrome OS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Current in-development features include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The network indicator&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;App launcher&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;App icons in the panel&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;The modern layout, similar to GNOME/Ubuntu/OS X&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Here’s a nice screenshot of our work so far, highlighting the classic layout and our fancy calendar indicator:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;responsive-img&quot; src=&quot;/images/monthly_update_1_15/screenshot_1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros-shell/graphs/contributors&quot;&gt;7 developers&lt;/a&gt; who have contributed to the desktop shell, and to the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-desktop/graphs/contributors&quot;&gt;3 developers&lt;/a&gt; who have contributed to the desktop backend code.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;ostree-and-app-bundles&quot;&gt;OSTree and App Bundles&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ve successfully set up building OSTree images from Arch packages, and have tested a GNOME OSTree image in VirtualBox. We’ve built a Papyros image too, but it’s having Wayland issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;This is huge step forward, as we now have the foundation for a fully atomic, stable, and read-only base OS using OSTree and Arch Linux. Awesome stuff! If you want try it out, check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/powerpack&quot;&gt;Powerpack&lt;/a&gt; repository, and follow the instructions in the README. The plan is to eventually start building the OSTree repository and VirtualBox images (plus eventually installable ISOs) on our build server, but for you now must compile it from scratch.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In addition OSTree providing the base operating system, we are also looking to using a new GNOME project called &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/alexlarsson/xdg-app&quot;&gt;xdg-app&lt;/a&gt;, which implements &lt;a href=&quot;https://wiki.gnome.org/Projects/SandboxedApps&quot;&gt;App Bundles and sandboxing&lt;/a&gt;. This will support the concept of runtimes, such as GNOME 3.16, Papyros 0.1, KDE 5.2, etc., which allow multiple versions installed side-by-side without breaking apps. This will allow applications to be upgraded independent of each other and the base OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;core-apps&quot;&gt;Core Apps&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Some work has started on the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/settings-app&quot;&gt;Settings app&lt;/a&gt;, but most of it is in the planning phase still.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The great news is an app developer has started on what will probably be the default Calculator app! Check out his code on &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/PierreJacquier/papyros-calculator&quot;&gt;GitHub&lt;/a&gt; or view his post on &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/117435800250066519130/posts/da2JuC1gkbN&quot;&gt;Google+&lt;/a&gt;. Here’s a screenshot of the Calculator app:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;responsive-img&quot; src=&quot;/images/monthly_update_1_15/papyros-calculator.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-website&quot;&gt;The Website&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In case you’re new to the project, or didn’t happen to notice, we have a new website! It’s built with the all-new Octopress 3, which is a static website generator built on top of Jekyll. We’re also slowly beginning to implement a Material Design theme using Polymer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you’re a web developer and interested in contributing, feel free to check out the &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros.github.io/issues&quot;&gt;GitHub Issues&lt;/a&gt; or &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros.github.io/pulls&quot;&gt;submit a pull request&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to the  &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros.github.io/graphs/contributors&quot;&gt;4 developers&lt;/a&gt; who have contributed to the  new website.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;getting-involved&quot;&gt;Getting Involved&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Interested in contributing to the project? We have a page for that! Check out our &lt;a href=&quot;/get_involved&quot;&gt;Get Involved&lt;/a&gt; page. Here you can find ways to contribute, regardless of whether you are a developer, designer, translator, tester, or just plain user.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also have a Donate button that page, which allows you to donate via Paypal. All donations will go to web hosting and server costs and (once we set them up) bug bounties.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks for everyone’s support and interest in our project! Here’s to another exciting month of development!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;br /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;– Michael Spencer, Papyros founder and lead developer&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 05 Feb 2015 21:33:45 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://papyros.io/monthly-update/2015/02/05/monthly-status-update-1-15.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://papyros.io/monthly-update/2015/02/05/monthly-status-update-1-15.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>monthly-update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Weekly Status Update</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Quantum OS has been renamed to Papyros to avoid trademark issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We’ll be starting weekly status updates to share progress on the various components of Quantum OS.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;qml-material&quot;&gt;QML Material&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;21 commits where made to our Material Design framework during the past week. The following features
were implemented:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Implement the Switch control and update the design to match Material Design [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@boghison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@iBeliever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Switch to GitFlow, and set up a CONTRIBUTING.md document [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@iBeliever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Load more of the Roboto fonts [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/glenfordwilliams&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/glenfordwilliams&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@glenfordwilliams&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Initial work on a component demo app [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@iBeliever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]
    &lt;ul&gt;
      &lt;li&gt;Initial demos cover the Button, Switch, Icon, and Progress Bar components&lt;/li&gt;
    &lt;/ul&gt;
  &lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Improvements to the Snackbar component [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@boghison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Ongoing work includes:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Migrating to QtQuick.Controls&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Rewriting the PageStack code to use QtQuick.Controls and sort out the way transitions, etc are handled [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material/issues/36&quot;&gt;#36&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material/issues/37&quot;&gt;#37&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Investigating how to handle the various styles of the Robot font [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material/issues/46&quot;&gt;#46&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thanks to all the developers who have contributed code to the project this week and in past weeks!
I’d like to especially mention &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/geiseri&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/geiseri&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@geiseri&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;  who has been helping us migrate to QtQuick.Controls along
with contributing other great feedback and discussion about how we’re implementing various features.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;quantum-shell&quot;&gt;Quantum Shell&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;No commits landed in the main branch for Quantum Shell, as discussion was ongoing and any work was made
to separate repositories or branches. The following items were discussed or worked on:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Implementing the Music indicator [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros-shell/issues/14&quot;&gt;#14&lt;/a&gt;, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros-shell/issues/16&quot;&gt;#16&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Implementing the Network indicator [&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/papyros-shell/issues/17&quot;&gt;#17&lt;/a&gt;]&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Planning also continues on different designs and layouts and deciding what features to implement.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;sddm-theme&quot;&gt;SDDM Theme&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Not much happening here, as the focus during the past week has been on other components. However, &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/boghison&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@boghison&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt; did turn the initial prototype into a working SDDM theme, which is awesome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;general-os-progress&quot;&gt;General OS progress&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;A large part of my time this week was spent on the following items:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Trying to get QtCompositor compiled and working on Arch Linux, which will be the base for our OS&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Studying and learning how to use OSTree, which will be the distribution/release technology used in Quantum OS&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Other ongoing issues include:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;ul&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Picking a new name. With the majority of my time spent on other tasks, I have not spent much time on this. I have several names to research in the US trademark databases and perform general internet seaches on. Currently, my favorite candidate is Papyros, as a modified version of papyrus, an ancient form of paper, which fits with Material Design and the concept of paper used.&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Getting a list of packages we will need to ship together&lt;/li&gt;
  &lt;li&gt;Designing various aspects of the desktop shell, applications, and OS in general&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;

&lt;p&gt;In closing, we’re making good progress towards building an awesome OS! Thanks to everyone interested in the project and who have offered support, ideas and suggestions, design feedback, or code contributions. That’s the power of open source!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have any suggestions, bug reports, or ideas for what you’d like to see next in the various projects? Comment here or on Google+, or open issues on our GitHub projects at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros&quot;&gt;https://github.com/papyros&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Christmas is coming up next week, so I may not do a progress report next Friday and will probably not make a whole lot of progress on Quantum OS work as well. I’ll be back in full force the next week, though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Have a blessed Christmas and a happy New Year!&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 20 Dec 2014 01:55:59 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://papyros.io/weekly-status/2014/12/20/weekly-status-update.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://papyros.io/weekly-status/2014/12/20/weekly-status-update.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>weekly-status</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Introduction and Initial Plans</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Welcome to Papyros! We are working on developing an operating system based upon Linux which conforms to Google’s &lt;a href=&quot;http://google.com/design/&quot;&gt;Material Design guidelines&lt;/a&gt;. The focus will be on creating a stable and easy-to-use operating system with a heavy emphasis on well-thought-out design.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;UPDATE:&lt;/strong&gt; Quantum OS has been renamed to Papyros to avoid trademark issues.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-desktop-shell&quot;&gt;The Desktop Shell&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We plan to develop the desktop shell and applications primarily using Qt 5 and QML, which will allow us to build highly polished and dynamic user interfaces and will work well for implementing Material Design. If possible, we will build the desktop shell in as much QML as possible built on top of the QtCompositor API, which provides a Qt framework for building a Wayland compositor.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We already have some working code with an experimental desktop layout:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;responsive-img&quot; src=&quot;/images/desktop_layout_1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;applications&quot;&gt;Applications&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Our application framework will be based upon a QML UI toolkit implementing Material Design. It is written completely from scratch, and does not use QtQuick Controls, and is not a fork or theme for the Ubuntu UI toolkit. The reason for this is that we want to be able to focus specifically on implementing Material Design, which has several unique features, such as the concept of elevation. We will most likely have a Qt/Gtk theme for existing apps, but the official recommendation will be writing new applications or porting existing applications to the Material Design framework. The API will be similar to that of other QML frameworks such as the Ubuntu UI toolkit, so it will not be too difficult porting existing apps.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The UI framework itself will be cross-platform, just as Qt itself is, so apps written with it will run on OS X, Windows, or other Linux distributions. This plays well with the concept of Material Design, which aims to be a cross-platform design framework.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We also plan to support web apps and treat them as nicely as possible. This will probably involve a simple wrapper that allows web apps to have their own icon and window with no browser chrome.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The Material Design QML framework is well underway, as can be seen from this sample application:&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img class=&quot;responsive-img&quot; src=&quot;/images/blueprint_1.png&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-base-operating-system&quot;&gt;The Base Operating System&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We plan to initially leverage an existing operating system, most likely Arch or Ubuntu. Arch is a strong possibility because of the simple packaging manager, lightweight base system, and the rolling release concept. Our goal is to base our work on the latest upstream versions available, with no patches or modifications, so our work will run on any base Linux distro that supports Wayland.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We will also need to build a login manager and installer. Our plan is to write a theme for SDDM, which supports themes written in QML. We don’t have any plans for an installer yet, as that will need to wait until a base OS is chosen.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h4 id=&quot;the-development-team-and-code&quot;&gt;The Development Team and Code&lt;/h4&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Currently the team consists of mainly just myself (&lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/+MichaelSpencer&quot;&gt;Michael Spencer&lt;/a&gt;/&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot;&gt;&lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/iBeliever&quot; class=&quot;user-mention&quot;&gt;@iBeliever&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/a&gt;), though I am already getting some great design feedback and mockups from &lt;a href=&quot;https://plus.google.com/u/0/+AndreaDelSarto88&quot;&gt;Andrea Del Sarto&lt;/a&gt;. Anyone who is interested in contributing code, design, feedback, or testing is welcome to contribute, though I plan to remain in control of project management to ensure that we stay focused on our goals. I am certainly open to suggestions and feedback, though!&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We are hosting our code on GitHub at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros&quot;&gt;https://github.com/papyros&lt;/a&gt;, with the Material Design QML framework hosted at &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material&quot;&gt;https://github.com/papyros/qml-material&lt;/a&gt;. You can also track our mockups &lt;a href=&quot;https://github.com/papyros/mockups&quot;&gt;here&lt;/a&gt;, though because of the flexibility and power of QML, we often work directly in code versus designing mockups first.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 20 Nov 2014 00:48:41 +0000</pubDate>
        <link>http://papyros.io/2014/11/20/introduction-and-initial-plans.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://papyros.io/2014/11/20/introduction-and-initial-plans.html</guid>
        
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
